This is Ojoch. Occupation - tomcat. Great lover
of comfort, delicious food and a good read.
Well, so the stock is going
up a little… oh noes, two
points down… what? … Crimea
occupied, are you kidding me?!
Yeah, and he really hates when
someone disturbs his comfort.
Auntie Soapie does
that all the time!
Ojoch, there is something
nasty going on in our neat
city and you are reading the newspaper?
Really??!!
Everytime Soapie says that,
the work is waiting.
No excuses! Get in and let’s fly!
No time to argue!
Meoooow, are you kidding?
I haven’t even finished
the sport news and we
should go to work? This
has to be joke. Yuck!
Come on, get in the magic bucket and let’s
fly and clean the city from all the mess.
And Ojch is already quietly sitting in his
flying bucked and following his owner.
Meooow, and who is it this time? Meoooow!
Overspice Stinkifoot! Making
a mess around the statue!!!!
One sock here, one sock there,
let’s spread the mess everywhere!
Overspice, I challange you to a fight!
Death or a broom! Ojoch, prepare bubbles!
Meooow!!! Now she needs me? Push the
button… such a complicated task!
I will not give up so easily!
You shall not wash me!
I could have stayed home. They
don’t need me here anyway!
And Ojoch eventually gave
up and let them fight.
Hmmm, maybe I could end the the
conflict a little different way?
Well, just a few bullets ...rat-tat-tat,
such cadence! weeeel, I could
handle it, but who would cook for me then?
And where would I live?
Meeeow, I guess not.
Ojoch will have to work out a better plan.
So he went away to think it over.
R.U.R., well what is it? War and peace
- well, who wrote this? All Quiet
on the Western Front - what a pulp fiction!
None of this will help me!
Look, this is it! Karel Gott's
Love Potion Number Ten!
This will solve all my problems.
So that’s the medium flame,
one plate, slightly overcook!
Just a pinch of ginger,
pinch of clove, a nutmeg.
Well, even Jamie Oliver
would be jealous!
What a nice smell!
Now just pour it into the kettle! Yes,
it has to look good, that is a must!
Yes, just dont spill anything now.
Over there,
jesus, carefully, carefully,
that’s so much love!
Heeeey!! Can you take a break for
a few minutes? It’s tea time!
Ojoch was happy, they bought it! He saw the
spark between them! But he hide, just in case.
He doesn’t have to see everything and also ...
what if it didn’t work out?
Overspice!
Soapie, my love!
Yeeeeees!!! Wohooo!! It worked!
Heaven on earth,
no work, that’s awesome!
Reallly…. Ha! Uh-oh!
Well, what just happened? Oh noeees!!!
Yes, Ojoch spread a lot of love along
the way, but no one expected that this
love would bring the statue to life. Or
that this statue would fall in love.
Yeah, yeah, I like you too but find someone
bigger, someone like you. Heeeeeelp!!! Meow!